When we think of a courageous pool
player, we think of a player that has no
fear. But this is actually a total
misconception because courage is not the
same as having no fear. Courage is
actually acting in the presence of fear.
Fear of mistakes, fear of embarrassment.
We all feel the same because as humans,
we all share the same emotions. Make no
mistake about it. The pros feel the same
fear from time to time. They're just
really good at jumping back into the
arena, putting themselves in new tough
positions so they can improve. And if
there's players out there that say
they're never afraid, they're lying. So,
how can you have more courage in your
game and in your life today? Put
yourself in the box again, perhaps in
that weekly tournament where you missed
last week on Hillh Hill or your league
night where everybody's watching you and
that makes you really anxious. You see,
that's how you grow. Acting in the
presence of fear. Keep going. Keep
showing up. Keep facing your fears. Be
courageous.